ILGWU. Upper South Department records 5780/039
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
ILGWU. Upper South Department records
1936-1974
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
Upper South Department
International Ladies' Garment Workers' Union
5780/039
11 cubic feet
11 linear ft.
Articles, correspondence, reports.
Contains records of the Upper South Department of the International Ladies' Garment Workers' Union, including correspondence, agreements, financial statements, and many files on joint boards, local unions, and conferences in the region. Joint Boards of Baltimore, Cleveland, and New York City are represented in the records of the Upper South Department. Locals represented in this subseries include: 4 (Baltimore, MD), 23-25 (New York, NY), 62 (New York, NY), 91 (New York, NY), 106 (Baltimore, MD), 110 (Baltimore, MD), 201 (Norfolk, VA), 236 (Appomattox, VA), 239 (Baltimore, MD), 247 (Rockwood, PA), 248 (Hebron and Sharpton, MD), 256 (Thurmont, MD), 260 (Pirnceton, WV), 264 (Grafton, WV), 267 (Glen Rock, PA), 293 (Portsmouth, VA), 312 (Harrisburg, PA), 316 (York, PA), 319 (Baltimore, MD), 327 (Baltimore, MD), 328 (Kokomo, IN), 362 (Baltimore, MD), 373 (Petersburg, MD), 393 (Westminster, MD), 400 (Roanoke, VA), 400, 413, 402 (Bristol, VA), 406 (Arlington, VA), 416 (Clarksburg, WV), 419 (Lynchburg, VA), 420 (Huntington, WV), 422 (Point Pleasant, WV), 425 (Martingsburg, WV), 430 (Martinsville, WV), 434 (Cumberland, MD), 435 (Hagerstown, MD), 438 (Winchester, VA), 464 (Buchanan, VA), 474 (Marion, VA), 504 (Crewe, VA), 561 (Bedford, VA), and 585 (Cambridge, MD).
5491388
General
Contact Information:
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation and Archives Martin P. Catherwood Library 227 Ives Hall Cornell University Ithaca, NY 14853 (607) 255-3183> kheel_center@cornell.edu http://www.ilr.cornell.edu/library/kheel
Compiled by:
Kheel Staff, October 07, 2008
EAD encoding:
Kathryn Dowgiewicz, June 26, 2013
Biographical / Historical
Founded in 1900 by local union delegates representing about 2,000 members in cities in the northeastern United States, the ILGWU grew in geographical scope, membership size, political influence to become one of the most powerful forces in American organized labor by mid-century. Representing workers in the women's garment industry, the ILGWU worked to improve working and living conditions of its members through collective bargaining agreements, training programs, health care facilities, cooperative housing, educational opportunities, and other efforts. In 1995, the ILGWU merged with the Amalgamated Clothing and Textile Workers Union (ACTWU) to form the Union of Needletrades, Industrial and Textile Employees (UNITE).
Biographical / Historical
Angela Bambace was born in Brazil in 1898. She joined the ILGWU in 1917 and became a member of Local 89 participating in the dressmakers' strike two years later. In 1941, Bambace was an organizer in the Maryland-Virginia District and elected the district's manager in 1942. Bambace became a vice president and member of the ILGWU General Executive Board in 1956. She remained manager of the district when it was renamed the Upper South Department in 1957 and continued until her retirement in 1972. Bambace died in 1975.
Biographical / Historical
The Upper South Department of the ILGWU began as the Maryland-Virginia District. Established in 1942, this district covered Maryland, Virginia, and West Virginia. The Baltimore Joint Board was not directly affiliated with the Maryland- Virginia District, but the two entities worked together closely and both were supervised by ILGWU Vice President Charles Kreindler. Sam Caplan was the manager of the Baltimore Joint Board and member of Pressers' Local 362. The Maryland-Virginia District was renamed the Upper South Department in 1957.
Angela Bambace served as the first manager of the Maryland-Virginia District, and later the Upper South Department, until her retirement in 1972. During her tenure, Irwin Jaffe served as the assistant manager of the Maryland-Virginia District. Sol Hoffman was manager from 1972 to 1977. Peter Nadash succeeded Hoffman, and was director of the Upper South Department at the time of the ILGWU's merger with ACTWU in 1995.
Locals associated with the Upper South Department include: Local 233 Richmond, VA; Local 235 Lawrenceville, VA; Local 236 Appomattox, VA; Local 238 Farmville, VA; Local 248 Hebron and Sharptown, MD; Local 260 Princeton, WV; Local 263 Danville, VA; Local 400 Roanoke, VA; Local 401 New Castle, VA; Local 402 Bristol, VA; Local 416 Clarksburg WV; Local 418 Parkersburg, WV; Local 419 Lynchburg, VA; Local 422 Pt. Pleasant, WV; Local 429 Grasonville, MD; Local 434 Cumberland, MD; Local 435 Hagerstown, MD; Local 438 Winchester, VA; Local 474 Marion, VA; Local 504 Crewe, VA; Local 517 Wheeling, WV. Baltimore Locals within the Baltimore Joint Board include: Locals 4, 110, 362, 327, 312, 316, 393, 239, and 106
Scope and Contents
The collection is arranged alphabetically by subject, company, organization or individual. There are agreements with local garment companies, files for organizations such as the AFL-CIO, and the American for Democratic Action (Angela Bambace was on the board of directors), information on other labor unions which the ILGWU worked with and supported during strikes through donations, correspondence with officers of the ILGWU including David Dubinsky, records of different departments (Eastern out of Town, Education, Legal, Political, Research), and various informal and official reports (such as the Upper South Education Dept. with information classes and costs).
Also with the records are documents detailing the expenses for strikes, minutes, agendas and proceedings for meetings and conferences of the Upper South Department, and rules, benefits and literature for the various Health Funds. There are numerous financial statements, assets and invoices for the Maryland Virginia District, Upper South Department, and Baltimore Joint Board. In fact, the collection consists of abundant material on the Baltimore Joint Board, and those interested in researching the Joint Board and Baltimore locals would find much information within this collection. Records of the Baltimore Joint Board include meeting minutes, financial statements, benefits and administration of the Health Fund, and correspondence to and from the manager.
A section of the collection contains files on manufacturing firms and garment companies within the jurisdiction of the Upper South Department. Included are contracts and agreements, grievances, and correspondence. Of particular note is the various contract disputes for the Kenrose Manufacturing Co. and the subsequent strike and dismissal of workers after the company opened a new plant in Ireland.
Another component to the collection is files for the various organizers and business agents of the Upper South Department. These files are arranged by individual and contain correspondence, organizing activities, expenses incurred while the organizers were on the road traveling, and an assortment of leaflets and flyers that were passed out or put in shops. Also included are the organizers weekly reports. These were forms filled out and turned in at the end of each week in which the organizer listed which shops were visited, how many workers were met, and how many union cards were sent out. The provided a day by day report of the organizer's activities.
While there are indeed folders devoted specifically to Bambace and her personal correspondence, letters, and awards, as the manager of the Department for numerous decades, the majority of all business correspondence, memos and reports originated from her as well. This is also true of the correspondence to and from Charles Kreindler, ILGWU vice president and manager of Local 25 Blouse and Waistmakers, NY who supervised the Departments and received reports.
Of particular interest is a folder of postcards, photos and v-mail, correspondence to and from ILGWU members who were serving in World War II. The men sent letters back to their locals and fellow union members, while the members and locals in turn responded by sending the men letters, copies of "Justice," and care packages. Much correspondence is from Pvt. L Benjamin Brager, who was the former secretary of Local 362 and who often addresses his letters "Dear ladies."
The records of the locals within the Department contain correspondence, financial statements, election material, rosters, and minutes of board meetings. Locals included in the collection: Local 4 Baltimore; Local 106 (Dressmakers) Baltimore, MD; Local 110 (Cutters) Baltimore, MD; Local 201 Norfolk, VA; Local 236 Appomattox, VA; Local 239 (Swiss Embroidery Workers) Baltimore, MD; Local 247 Rockwood, PA; Local 248 Hebron and Sharptown, MD: Local 256 Thurmont, MD: Local 260 Princeton, WV; Local 264 Grafton, WV; Local 267 Glen Rock, PA; Local 293 Portsmouth, VA; Local 312 Harrisburg, PA; Local 316 York, PA; Local 319 Baltimore, MD; Local 327 Baltimore, MD; Local 362 (Pressers) Baltimore, MD; Local 373 Petersburg, MD; Local 393 Westminster, MD; Local 400 Roanoke, VA; Local 402 Bristol, VA; Local 406 Arlington, VA; Local 416 Clarksburg, WV; Local 419 Lynchburg, VA; Local 420 Huntington, WV; Local 422 Pt. Pleasant, WV; Local 425 Martinsburg, WV; Local 430 Martinsville, WV; Local 434 Cumberland, MD; Local 435 Hagerstown, MD; Local 438 Winchester, VA; Local 464 Buchanan, VA; Local 424 Marion, VA; Local 504 Crewe, VA; Local 561 Bedford, VA; Local 585 Cambridge, MD.
Conditions Governing Access
Access to the collections in the Kheel Center is restricted. Please contact a reference archivist for access to these materials.
Related Materials
Related Collections: 5780: ILGWU records
Women's clothing industry -- United States; Women's clothing industry -- Maryland -- Baltimore; Clothing workers -- Labor unions -- United States; Clothing workers -- Labor unions -- Maryland -- Baltimore; Clothing workers -- United States; Clothing workers -- Maryland -- Baltimore; Industrial relations -- United States; Industrial relations -- Maryland -- Baltimore; International Ladies' Garment Workers' Union. -- Upper South Department.; International Ladies' Garment Workers' Union. -- Baltimore Joint Board.
5491388
- A, 1940-1964 (Box 1, Folder 1)
- Agreements [folder 1 of 3], 1937-1968 (Box 1, Folder 2a)
  Scope and Contents
  Samples.
- Agreements [folder 2 of 3], 1937-1968 (Box 1, Folder 2b)
- Agreements [folder 3 of 3], 1937-1968 (Box 1, Folder 2c)
- AFL and AFL-CIO, 1946-1961 (Box 1, Folder 3)
- AFL Political Education, League of (Virginia), 1949-1953 (Box 1, Folder 4)
- Americans for Democratic Action (Baltimore Chapter), 1947-1949 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  Incl. minutes of board of directors.
- Auto Workers Strike Fund, 1946 (Box 1, Folder 6)
- B, 1940-1966 (Box 1, Folder 7)
- Baltimore Council of AFL-CIO Unions, 1959-1967 (Box 1, Folder 8)
- Baltimore Federation of Labor, 1940-1951 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  Leaflets.
- Bambace, Angela. Personal [folder 1 of 2], 1940-1970 (Box 1, Folder 10)
  Corres., awards, photographs.
- Bambace, Angela. Personal [folder 2 of 2], 1940-1970 (Box 1, Folder 11)
- Bambace, Angela. Speeches. n.d. (Box 1, Folder 12)
- C, 1946-1970 (Box 1, Folder 13)
- Caplan, Samuel, 1942-1949 (Box 2, Folder 1)
  Incl. testimonial dinners, 1946, 1949.
- Children's Dress, Cotton Dress and Sportswear Contractors' Association, 1966 (Box 2, Folder 2)
- Complaints, 1944-1970 (Box 2, Folder 3)
- Constitution and By-laws, 1947 (Box 2, Folder 4)
  Maryland-Virginia District. Upper South (n.d.); and Baltimore Jt. Bd. (n.d.).
- D, 1940-1970 (Box 2, Folder 5)
- Daniels, Wilbur, 1960-1966 (Box 2, Folder 6)
- Dinner, Charles Kreindler, 1956 (Box 2, Folder 7)
  Dec. 13, 1956. Testimonial Dinner on behalf of City of Hope.
- Dinner, Charles Kreindler, 1958 (Box 2, Folder 8)
  Israeli bonds.
- Dubinsky, David, 1940-1948 (Box 2, Folder 9)
  Incl. complaints and reports.
- Dubinsky, David, 1949-1962 (Box 2, Folder 10)
- Dubinsky, David, 1963-1966 (Box 2, Folder 11)
- E, 1945-1963 (Box 2, Folder 12)
- Eastern Region, 1954-1964 (Box 3, Folder 1)
- Edelman, Jacob, 1945-1955 (Box 3, Folder 2)
  Incl. corres. re negotiations.
- Education Dept. Upper South Dept., 1948-1961 (Box 3, Folder 3)
- Education Dept. Upper South Dept., 1944-1969 (Box 3, Folder 4)
  Incl. reports, leaflets, articles.
- Elections, Union, 1962-1965 (Box 3, Folder 5)
  Incl. ballots, some undated.
- F, 1944-1970 (Box 3, Folder 6)
- Federation of Union Representatives, 1961 (Box 3, Folder 7)
- Financial Statements. Baltimore Jt. Bd., 1944-1947 (Box 3, Folder 8)
- Financial Statements. Baltimore Jt. Bd., 1948-1950 (Box 3, Folder 9)
- Financial Statements. Baltimore Jt. Bd., 1951-1955 (Box 3, Folder 10)
- Financial Statements. Maryland-Virginia District, 1942-1950 (Box 3, Folder 11)
- Financial Statements. Upper South Dept., 1949-1953 (Box 3, Folder 12)
- Financial Statements. Upper South Dept., 1954-1962 (Box 3, Folder 13)
- Financial Statements. Locals of Department, 1947-1950 (Box 4, Folder 1)
- Financial Statements., 1947-1949 (Box 4, Folder 2)
  Incl. vouchers.
- Firms. Anderson Bros. Consolidated Co., Inc. (Danville, Va.) [folder 1 of 2], 1946-1951 (Box 4, Folder 3)
- Firms. Anderson Bros. Consolidated Co., Inc. (Danville, Va.) [folder 2 of 2], 1946-1951 (Box 4, Folder 4)
- Firms. Claire Frock Co. (Thurmont, Md.), 1949-1951 (Box 4, Folder 5)
- Firms. S. Cohen and Sons (Baltimore, Md.), 1937-1951 (Box 4, Folder 6)
- Firms. Climber land Undergarment Co. (Cumberland, Md.), 1936-1950 (Box 4, Folder 7)
  Incl. price settlements.
- Firms. Duti-Duds (Lynchburg, Va.), 1946 (Box 4, Folder 8)
- Firms. E-Z Thread Co. (Portsmouth, Va.), 1950-1951 (Box 4, Folder 9)
- Firms. Harris Dress Co. [folder 1 of 2], 1942-1949 (Box 4, Folder 10)
- Firms. Harris Dress Co. [folder 1 of 2], 1942-1949 (Box 4, Folder 11)
- Firms. Kenrose Mfg. Co. (Roanoke, Va.). [folder 1 of 8], 1945-1965 (Box 4, Folder 12)
  (Formerly Benrose Mfg. Co.) Incl. corres. re 1960 strike? Kenrose Clothesline, Nos. 14-24.
- Firms. Kenrose Mfg. Co. (Roanoke, Va.). [folder 2 of 8], 1945-1965 (Box 4, Folder 13)
- Firms. Kenrose Mfg. Co. (Roanoke, Va.). [folder 3 of 8], 1945-1965 (Box 4, Folder 14)
- Firms. Kenrose Mfg. Co. (Roanoke, Va.). [folder 4 of 8], 1945-1965 (Box 4, Folder 15)
- Firms. Kenrose Mfg. Co. (Roanoke, Va.). [folder 5 of 8], 1945-1965 (Box 5, Folder 1)
- Firms. Kenrose Mfg. Co. (Roanoke, Va.). [folder 6 of 8], 1945-1965 (Box 5, Folder 2)
- Firms. Kenrose Mfg. Co. (Roanoke, Va.). [folder 7 of 8], 1945-1965 (Box 5, Folder 3)
- Firms. Kenrose Mfg. Co. (Roanoke, Va.). [folder 8 of 8], 1945-1965 (Box 5, Folder 4)
- Firms. L'Aiglon (Hagerstown, Md.), 1947-1950 (Box 5, Folder 5)
- Firms. Maidenform (Princeton, W. Va.), 1944-1946 (Box 5, Folder 6)
- Firms. Louis Marcus Corp. (Baltimore, Md.), 1944-1949 (Box 5, Folder 7)
- Firms. Marion Mfg. Co. (Marion, Va.) [folder 1 of 4], 1947-1954 (Box 5, Folder 8)
- Firms. Marion Mfg. Co. (Marion, Va.) [folder 2 of 4], 1947-1954 (Box 5, Folder 9)
- Firms. Marion Mfg. Co. (Marion, Va.) [folder 3 of 4], 1947-1954 (Box 5, Folder 10)
- Firms. Marion Mfg. Co. (Marion, Va.) [folder 4 of 4], 1947-1954 (Box 5, Folder 11)
- Firms. Morris and Co. (Baltimore, Md.), 1946-1947 (Box 5, Folder 12)
  Incl. piece rate settlements.
- Firms. Mt. Marion Fashions (Marion, Va.), 1948-1950 (Box 5, Folder 13)
- Firms. Perfect Garment Co. (Baltimore, Md.), 1942-1954 (Box 6, Folder 1)
  Incl. Rock Mfg. Co. (Glen Rock, Pa.).
- Firms. Perfection Garment Co. Martinsburg, W. Va.) [folder 1 of 3], 1942-1960 (Box 6, Folder 2)
  Incl. The Needle's Eve. 1948. 1949 (2 issues).
- Firms. Perfection Garment Co. Martinsburg, W. Va.) [folder 2 of 3], 1942-1960 (Box 6, Folder 3)
- Firms. Perfection Garment Co. Martinsburg, W. Va.) [folder 3 of 3], 1942-1960 (Box 6, Folder 4)
- Firms. Puritan Mills (Roanoke, Va.), 1944-1954 (Box 6, Folder 5)
- Firms. Quality Mfg. Co. (Pt. Pleasant, W. Va.), 1945-1947 (Box 6, Folder 6)
- Firms. Reliance Mfg. Co. (Huntington, W. Va.) [folder 1 of 2], 1944-1950 (Box 6, Folder 7)
- Firms. Reliance Mfg. Co. (Huntington, W. Va.) [folder 2 of 2], 1944-1950 (Box 6, Folder 8)
- Firms. Rutledge Mfg. Co. (Baltimore, Md.) [folder 1 of 2], 1951-1961 (Box 6, Folder 9)
- Firms. Rutledge Mfg. Co. (Baltimore, Md.) [folder 2 of 2], 1951-1961 (Box 6, Folder 10)
- Firms. Seldin Coat Co. (Baltimore, Md.), 1942-1954 (Box 6, Folder 11)
- Firms. Virginia-Carolina Chemical Corp. Bag Dept. (Richmond, Va.), 1946-1947 (Box 6, Folder 12)
- Firms. Yunker Mfg. Co. (Pt. Pleasant, Va.) [folder 1 of 3], 1946-1966 (Box 7, Folder 1)
- Firms. Yunker Mfg. Co. (Pt. Pleasant, Va.) [folder 2 of 3], 1946-1966 (Box 7, Folder 2)
- Firms. Yunker Mfg. Co. (Pt. Pleasant, Va.) [folder 3 of 3], 1946-1966 (Box 7, Folder 3)
- Form Letters, circulars and leaflets [folder 1 of 3], 1940-1961 (Box 7, Folder 4)
  Baltimore Jt. Bd., Md.-Va. District, Upper South Dept.
- Form Letters, circulars and leaflets [folder 2 of 3], 1940-1961 (Box 7, Folder 5)
- Form Letters, circulars and leaflets [folder 3 of 3], 1940-1961 (Box 7, Folder 6)
- G, 1944-1970 (Box 7, Folder 7)
- General Executive Board, 1944-1967 (Box 7, Folder 8)
  Contains issues of ILG'er, 1944-1946.
- Greenfield, David. Upper South Dept., 1961-1969 (Box 7, Folder 9)
- H, 1946-1968 (Box 7, Folder 10)
- Health and Welfare Fund, Upper South Dept., Md.-Va. District, 1945-1971 (Box 7, Folder 11)
  Rules and regulations.
- Health Fund. Baltimore Coat and Suit Industry and Md.-Va. District, 1944-1974 (Box 7, Folder 12)
  Corres.
- Firms. Winchester Knitting Mills (Winchester, Va.), 1946-1949 (Box 7, Folder 13)
- Health Fund. Baltimore Coat and Suit Industry and Md.-Va. District [folder 1 of 3], 1945-1971 (Box 8, Folder 1)
  Administration Comm. minutes.
- Health Fund. Baltimore Coat and Suit Industry and Md.-Va. District [folder 2 of 3], 1945-1971 (Box 8, Folder 2)
- Health Fund. Baltimore Coat and Suit Industry and Md.-Va. District [folder 3 of 3], 1945-1971 (Box 8, Folder 3)
- Health Fund. Baltimore Coat and Suit Industry and Md.-Va. District, 1951-1957 (Box 8, Folder 4)
  Bd. of Trustees minutes.
- Health Fund. Baltimore Coat and Suit Industry and Md.-Va. District, 1944-1959 (Box 8, Folder 5)
  Financial statements.
- Hudson Shore Labor School, 1946-1950 (Box 8, Folder 6)
- I, 1940-1958 (Box 8, Folder 7)
- The ILGer, 1944-1961 (Box 8, Folder 8)
  Newsletter of Dept.
- ILGWU Conventions, 1947-1968 (Box 8, Folder 9)
- ILGWU Education Dept., 1945-1959 (Box 8, Folder 10)
- ILGWU Legal Dept., 1954-1966 (Box 8, Folder 11)
  Incl. corres. re Waxman case.
- ILGWU Management-Engineering Dept, 1946-1969 (Box 8, Folder 12)
- ILGWU Master Agreement Dept., 1966-1970 (Box 8, Folder 13)
- ILGWU Political Dept., 1947-1966 (Box 8, Folder 14)
- ILGWU Research Dept., 1942-1961 (Box 8, Folder 15)
- ILGWU Training Institute, 1950-1958 (Box 8, Folder 16)
- ILGWU Union Label Dept., 1960-1963 (Box 8, Folder 17)
- J, 1940-1965 (Box 9, Folder 1)
  Incl. Judy Bond reports.
- Jaffe, Irwin [folder 1 of 4], 1945-1962 (Box 9, Folder 2)
  Incl. corres. as organizer and asst. Mgr., Md.-Va. District; organizing leaflets for Reliance Mfg. Co.
- Jaffe, Irwin [folder 2 of 4], 1945-1962 (Box 9, Folder 3)
- Jaffe, Irwin [folder 3 of 4], 1945-1962 (Box 9, Folder 4)
- Jaffe, Irwin [folder 4 of 4], 1945-1962 (Box 9, Folder 5)
- Joint Boards. Baltimore, Md., 1946 (Box 9, Folder 6)
- Joint Boards. Baltimore, Md. Grievance Committee. Minutes., 1944-1952 (Box 9, Folder 7)
  Minutes of hearings.
- Joint Boards. Baltimore, Md. Sick Benefit Fund. Minutes., 1938-1939 (Box 9, Folder 8)
- Joint Boards. Baltimore, Md. Minutes., 1941-1943 (Box 9, Folder 9)
- Joint Boards. Baltimore, Md. Minutes., 1944-1946 (Box 9, Folder 10)
- Joint Boards. Baltimore, Md. Minutes., 1947-1948 (Box 9, Folder 11)
- Joint Boards. Baltimore, Md. Minutes., 1949-1950 (Box 9, Folder 12)
- Joint Boards. Baltimore, Md. Minutes., 1951-1952 (Box 9, Folder 13)
- Joint Boards. Baltimore, Md. Minutes., 1953 (Box 10, Folder 1)
- Joint Boards. Baltimore, Md. Minutes., 1954-1955 (Box 10, Folder 2)
  Some undated.
- Joint Boards. Baltimore, Md. Sick Benefit Fund. Minutes., 1941-1945 (Box 10, Folder 3)
- Joint Boards. Baltimore, Md. Sick Benefit Fund., 1942-1945 (Box 10, Folder 4)
  Sick Benefit Fund, Locals 4, 110, 319, 362; financial statements.
- Joint Boards. Cleveland, 1948-1950 (Box 10, Folder 5)
  Corres., re Quality Mfg. Co., Pt. Pleasant, W. Va.
- Joint Boards. New York Dress, 1945-1959 (Box 10, Folder 6)
  Incl. Dressmakers' Joint Council.
- K, 1940-1959 (Box 10, Folder 7)
- Kreindler, Charles [folder 1 of 4], 1940-1950 (Box 10, Folder 8)
  Corres. and reports.
- Kreindler, Charles [folder 2 of 4], 1940-1950 (Box 10, Folder 9)
- Kreindler, Charles [folder 3 of 4], 1940-1950 (Box 10, Folder 10)
- Kreindler, Charles [folder 4 of 4], 1940-1950 (Box 10, Folder 11)
- L, 1945-1969 (Box 10, Folder 12)
- Lists (n.d.). (Box 10, Folder 13)
  Officers and exec. bd. members of locals; workers in shops.
- Local 4. Baltimore, Md., 1944-1962 (Box 10, Folder 14)
  Incl. election ballots (1944, 1947, 1950, 1962).
- Local 4. Baltimore, Md., 1943-1948 (Box 11, Folder 1)
  Exec. bd. minutes, Appeal Committee (1944).
- Local 4. Baltimore, Md., 1945-1954 (Box 11, Folder 2)
- Local 23-25. NYC, 1965-1966 (Box 11, Folder 3)
- Local 62. NYC, 1956-1964 (Box 11, Folder 4)
- Local 91. NYC, 1963-1967 (Box 11, Folder 5)
- Local 106. Baltimore, Md., 1942-1950 (Box 11, Folder 6)
  Exec. bd. minutes, constitution and by-laws (n.d.).
- Local 106. Baltimore, Md., 1942-1950 (Box 11, Folder 7)
  Incl. corres. re Ruth Murray case.
- Local 106. Baltimore, Md., 1942-1953 (Box 11, Folder 8)
- Local 106. Baltimore, Md., 1942 (Box 11, Folder 9)
  Financial statements, Sick Benefit Fund.
- Local 110. Baltimore, Md., 1951-1970 (Box 11, Folder 10)
  Jan. 3, 1951-Apr. 1, 1970. Minutes.
- Local 110. Baltimore, Md., 1947-1962 (Box 11, Folder 11)
  Incl. minutes of exec. bd. (1949).
- Local 110. Baltimore, Md., 1946-1954 (Box 11, Folder 12)
- Local 201. Norfolk, Va., 1942-1950 (Box 11, Folder 13)
- Local 236. Appomattox, Va., 1945-1963 (Box 11, Folder 14)
  Incl. minutes (1961, 1963).
- Local 239. Baltimore, Md., 1942-1946 (Box 11, Folder 15)
- Local 239. Baltimore, Md., 1944-1953 (Box 11, Folder 16)
  Financial statements, incl. Sick Benefit Fund (1944-45).
- Local 239. Baltimore, Md., 1946-1947 (Box 12, Folder 1)
  Transcript of hearing on charges against Miriam Billings before a GEB special committee (Feb. 14, 1947); incl, resolution re resignations of six organizers (1946).
- Local 247. Rockwood, Pa., 1954-1960 (Box 12, Folder 2)
  Financial statements, 1954-57.
- Local 248. Hebron and Sharptown, Md., 1954-1961 (Box 12, Folder 3)
  Incl. exec. bd. minutes, Nov. 11, 1959-Aug. 22, 1961; financial statements, 1954-57.
- Local 248. Hebron and Sharptown, Md., 1950-1959 (Box 12, Folder 4)
  Case presented to NLRB. incl. workers' statements.
- Local 256. Thurmont, Md., 1949-1954 (Box 12, Folder 5)
  Incl. leaflets for organizing drive, 1949.
- Local 260. Princeton, W. Va., 1960 (Box 12, Folder 6)
  Minutes.
- Local 264. Grafton, W. Va., 1957-1961 (Box 12, Folder 7)
  Minutes, Nov. 9, 1961.
- Local 267. Glen Rock, Pa., 1946-1950 (Box 12, Folder 8)
- Local 293. Portsmouth, Va., 1949-1951 (Box 12, Folder 9)
- Local 312. Harrisburg, Pa., 1942-1960 (Box 12, Folder 10)
- Local 316. York, Pa., 1942-1956 (Box 12, Folder 11)
- Local 319. Baltimore, Md., 1940-1944 (Box 12, Folder 12)
  Exec. Bd. minutes.
- Local 319, 1942-1944 (Box 12, Folder 13)
- Local 327. Baltimore, Md., 1950 (Box 12, Folder 14)
- Local 362, Baltimore, Maryland [folder 1 of 3], 1939-1949 (Box 13, Folder 1)
- Local 362, Baltimore, Maryland [folder 1 of 3], 1939-1949 (Box 13, Folder 2)
- Local 362, Baltimore, Maryland [folder 3 of 3], 1939-1949 (Box 13, Folder 3)
- Local 373, Petersburg, Maryland, 1944-1948 (Box 13, Folder 4)